{
    "id": "bd3c2c9da7344708998d7056fccec26b",
    "title": "Opposites Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Coffee is a stimulant while opium is a .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "retardant",
                "sedative",
                "pacifier"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The peacock is beautiful, but the ostrich is .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ugly",
                "plain",
                "clumsy",
                "dirty"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The tiger is carnivorous whereas the cow is .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "viviparous",
                "omnivorous",
                "herbivorous"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The like poles of a magnet …………………. while unlike poles attract.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "detest",
                "rival",
                "repel",
                "disgust"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Love is a virtue while hatred is a .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wise",
                "vise",
                "vice"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The road ascends to the top of the hill and then ...................... to the plain on the other side.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "condescends",
                "concedes",
                "descends"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "These rules are too rigid. We need more .....................… ones.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lucid",
                "timid",
                "flexible"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Kindness is admired, but cruelty is .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wicked",
                "despised",
                "disgusted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Some parts are separable from the whole and some are .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "imseparable",
                "unseparable",
                "inseparable"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not oppose or ....................... a government blindly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "approve",
                "support",
                "join",
                "disapprove"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}